const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "Who is the father of C language?  ",
    answers: ["Richard Branson", "Bjarne Stroustrap", "Dennis Ritchie", "James A. gosling"],
    correct: "Dennis Ritchie",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      'How many keywords is present in C language"?',
    answers: ["0","32","48","255"],
    correct: "32",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many types of loop in C?",
    answers: ["one","two","three","none"],
    correct: "three",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: "who is the developer of JAVA?",
    answers: [
     "Dennis Ritchie",
     "James Gosling",
     "Bjarne Stroustrup",
     "Charles Babbage"
    ],
    correct: "James Gosling",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "What was Java name before?",
    answers: ["Java", "Javax","Classes and java","Oak"],
    correct: "Oak",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which year Java was developed?",
    answers: [
      "1991","1972","1979","1995"
    ],
    correct: "1991",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What name represents the letter "M" in the NATO phonetic alphabet?',
    answers: ["Mike", "Matthew", "Mark", "Max"],
    correct: "Mike",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first version of Java?",
    answers: [
      "JDK alpha & Beta",
      "JDK 1.0","JDK 15","all of the above"
    ],
    correct: "JDK alpha & Beta",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "In java, scanner class is defined in ?",
    answers: [
      "java.util.package",
      "java.lang.package",
      "java.io.package",
      "all of above"
    ],
    correct: "java.util.package",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Scanner class is used to take input at ?",
    answers: [
      "compile-time",
      "run-time",
      "both a and b",
      "none of them"
    ],
    correct: "run-time",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "which loop always execute always once, even condition is false?",
    answers: [
      "while loop",
      "do while loop",
      "for loop",
      "for each loop"
    ],
    correct: "do while loop",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "do while loop is also known as?",
    answers: [
      "entry control",
      "exit control",
      "both a and b",
      "none"
    ],
    correct: "exit control",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "which of the following loops are entry controlled loops?",
    answers: [
      "while",
      "do while",
      "for loop",
      "both a and c"
    ],
    correct: "both a and c",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "which loop is best suitable for Arrays in java?",
    answers: [
      "for loop",
      "for-each loop",
      "while loop",
      "do while loop"
    ],
    correct: "for-each loop",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "Whhich of the following is not a part of binary operator?",
    answers: [
      "assignment operator",
      "arithmetic operator",
      "relational operator",
      "logical operator"
    ],
    correct: "assignment operator",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a arithmetic operator?",
    answers: [
      "+","*","%","&"
    ],
    correct: "&",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "How many types of logical operators in java?",
    answers: [
        "two",
        "three",
        "four",
        "none"
    ],
    correct: "three",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Relational operator is used for? ",
    answers: [
      "comparison",
      "assignment",
      "finding errors",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    correct: "comparison",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "which of the following is Bitwise AND operator?",
    answers: [
      "&&","||","!","&"
    ],
    correct: "&",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used for alternate of if-else statement?",
    answers: [
     "arithmetic operator",
     "bitwise operator",
     "ternary operator",
     "increment/decrement operator"
    ],
    correct: "ternary operator",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'What is default value of static variable ?',
    answers: [
      "0.0","0","garbage","random value"
    ],
    correct: "0",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: "A variable which is declared inside the method is called as ?",
    answers: [
      "instance variable",
      "local variable",
      "static variable",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    correct: "local variable",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these selection statements test only for Equality?",
    answers: [
      "if",
      "switch",
      "if & switch",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    correct: "switch",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which stream is used for input in java?",
    answers: [
      "System.out", 
      "System.in",
      "Scanner",
      "System"
    ],
    correct: "System.in",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question: "Which scanner class method is used to read integer value?",
    answers: [
      "nextInt()",
      "next()",
      "readInt()",
      "nextInteger()"
    ],
    correct: "nextInt()",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: "how many primitive datatype in java?",
    answers: [
      "4",
      "6","7","8"
    ],
    correct: "8",
    questionId: "2510086"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the size of char datatype in java?",
    answers: [
     "1 byte","2 byte","4 byte","8 byte"
    ],
    correct: "2 byte",
    questionId: "2685745"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the default value of boolean datatyped in java?",
    answers: [
      "true","false","depend on the system"
    ],
    correct: "false",
    questionId: "2796884"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is smallest integer datatype?",
    answers: [
      "short",
      "int",
      "long",
      "byte"
    ],
    correct: "byte",
    questionId: "2838900"
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following datatypes come under floating datatypes?',
    answers: [
      "long",
      "float","double","both b & c"
    ],
    correct: "both b & c",
    questionId: "298060"
  },
  {
    question: "what is the range of byte datatype is ?",
    answers: [
      "-128 to 128",
      "-127 to 128",
      "-128 to 127",
      "-127 to 127"
    ],
    correct: "-128 to 127",
    questionId: "3096579"
  },
  {
    question: "A constructor is called whenever?",
    answers: [
     "an object is declared",
     "an object is used",
     "class is declard ",
     "class is used"
    ],
    correct: "an object is declared",
    questionId: "3182461"
  },
  {
    question: "which of the following remarks about the differences between constructors and destructors are correct?",
    answers: [
    "Constructors can take arguements but destructors cannot",
    "Constructors can be overloaded but destructors cannot be overloaded",
    "Destructors can take arguements but constructors cannot",
    "Both a & b"
    ],
    correct: "Both a & b",
    questionId: "3239112"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct statement regarding inline functions?",
    answers: [
      "it speeds up execution",
      "it slows down execution",
      "it increases the code size",
      "both a and c"
    ],
    correct: "both a and c",
    questionId: "3318503"
  },
  
  {
    question: "How many types of polymorphism?",
    answers: [
      "one",
      "two",
      "three",
      "none"
    ],
    correct: "two",
    questionId: "4982981"
  }
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
